Hey everyone, thanks for listening to
the Grow Your Life podcast. My name is
Jeremiah Kowski. On this podcast, I help
coaches, mentors, trainers, service
providers get more leads, make more
money online, and get the results that
they want. I show you how to use
artificial intelligence to help augment
your own work, and how to still keep the
personal touch that you're wanting, that
you love, and that produces the results
for you. Now, today we're going to talk
about using AI to get more leads. AI is
not new. Uh AI is here to stay. And so
what we're going to start doing from
here on out is start treating AI the
same way that we would Microsoft Word.
You know, using computers, Microsoft
Word, uh email, those were new
technologies in the 1990s and people
were just like resistant of them.
Shopping online was seen as taboo and
things like that. The internet was seen
as only a way to get pornography for the
longest time. And AI has kind of been
taboo in many spaces
for the last 5 years. I've been using AI
for almost 5 years now since GPT3.
And I've been learning how to use it the
right way. We use it in every single
aspect of our business and with all of
our clients. And so I want to show you a
why I think that it's important to use
it. It's a tool just like email. It's a
tool just like Microsoft Word for you to
get the results that you want. But what
I use it for the most is for generating
leads and for getting more clients in my
business. When I'm actually delivering
content, it's still me talking. It's
still me streaming. It's still me
sharing. This is not an AI avatar of me
talking to you right now. This is
actually me talking. But what I do to
generate leads is I use it to come up
with ideas for how to communicate in a
way that's going to connect with my
prospects. So, when it comes to
generating leads,
everybody out there in the business
world is competing for your customers
attention.
Your customers exist. Your clients
exist,
but there are a bunch of other people
competing for their attention. And all
of them that are succeeding, I know this
for a fact because I've talked with
them, are using artificial intelligence.
They are using AI
to get more customers and more clients.
And so, how do they do this? Well, they
do it by figuring out how to communicate
better with their prospects. Right now,
artificial intelligence is a great
communications tool is what it is. It
allows you to take your ideas, your
goals, and filter it in a way that
communicates faster and better with the
people that you're looking for. So, what
we look at is if we go over to chat GPT,
it's one of the currently as of today,
it's the best AI that's out there. Uh,
Chat GPT actually just launched their
brand new GPT5 right here, which is
amazing. At the time of this recording,
this just launched yesterday and we're
we're actually really loving it for what
we're doing. We used it for emails. We
use it for blog posts. We use it for
content creation. We use it to come up
with our lead magnets. And so again,
what can you do for this? Well, first
off, again, I show people all the time,
you can use it to, you know, help me
identify the best niches to make a lead
magnet
on Facebook and Instagram, you know, and
it can give you these ideas. By the way,
the new GPT5 is way faster than anything
else that's out there.
This is actually pulling from some of my
uh own stuff that we've created with
clients. In fact, some of these ideas
for stuff that we've helped people with.
So, this is actually pulling some of
those ideas up for certain niches based
on my own usage of chat GPT. Um, so
let's say that you help special needs
parenting
uh generate for me a complete
marketing plan to get more leads using
social media for this niche.
And this is really what you can do now
with GPT5 is you can just ask it to come
up with a big picture idea and it will
now start to generate you little picture
ideas for each level right here.
So it's talking about generating, you
know, who's your audience, the core
strategy, we're going to use ads to a
lead magnet, get people on your email
list, and then a conversion offer, which
is again how I would do it. Exactly. Uh,
the calm corner toolkit, 7-day sensory
routine, communication breakthrough
guide. I actually like this right here.
Okay. Generate me an outline of the
communication breakthrough guide.
So, this is where we come up with an
idea for our lead magnet. Now, the AI
can help us come up with an outline for
what that looks like. And then, this is
where you could filter your own content
into here. There's a great tool that I
use called Otter AI which transcribes
all of my content that I use that we use
with our clients. It automatically takes
all of our Zoom calls and brings them in
here. This is uh with one of our clients
that we've worked with for stocks and
women's mentoring right here as well. If
you don't want to pay money for Otter
AI, you can always go to YouTube,
upload your video to YouTube, any video
that you upload to YouTube. Hey
everyone, thanks for listening to the
>> We'll have a transcript.
Find the transcript
>> by clicking over here going to more
scrolling down and you will find
transcript.
Can turn off the timestamps right here
and now you can copy a transcript from
any video on YouTube and then you just
paste that right into your AI right
here. So let's say let's say I want to
start a new chat and I want to say
generate me a marketing plan for a lead
magnet based on this transcripts
content. I'm going to paste the
transcript right here from a video that
I already created and it's going to come
up with a lead magnet around this. It
says okay 30-minute training the art of
lead getting turn your email list into a
client getting machine which is exactly
lead magnet that we recently launched
which is amazing. get 1,000 subscribers
in 30 minutes with a big following
without a big following. And in fact,
that is a brand new lead magnet that we
launched right here
already.
The art of lead getting how to get
thousand subscribers in 30 minutes. So,
the AI is already picking up on that
from a video transcript and the content
that we have created right there. Let's
go back to our original lead magnet
right here and let's say generate
me some sales copy for a landing page.
Use all best practices for sales
copywriting
including the
PAS ADA frame framework and epiphany
bridge as your foundation for writing.
Okay. So, we're just going to kind of
come up with that right here. So, we
have our hook, we have our sub headline,
we have our different sections.
End the battles of 10 word for word
scripts. 10 word for word scripts to
calm the power struggle with your child.
Parenting a neurode divergent child
isn't like the books say. These 10 write
scripts give you instant calming words
for the hardest moments. Does this sound
familiar? You ask your child to do
something. It turns
off. It could be exhausting. The worst
part every day feels like the same
struggle. Here we're amplifying it. I
used to believe it was just explained
better, more firmer. And so you would
literally take this and just put this
into a framework right here. The beauty
is we used to have to do this with
multiple prompts. Now with GPT5, it's
literally doing it with one prompt where
it's pulling all of this into and this
would be actually good enough for a
landing page that we would do right
there. And now what we do is we want to
create that into a landing page. You
have a few options to do this. Um you
can use Squarespace to put a page
together. Squarespace has their own
Squarespace AI that can generate landing
pages for you. You click get started
here on Squarespace. You tell it, okay,
we're going to be doing consulting.
That's probably one of the better ones
that we do right here. Um, we're going
to build a community,
get appointments, sell memberships,
build a template with blueprint AI right
here,
and then here we go. is it generated us
a template for a website right there.
Let's see. We can do
brand personality.
Get this right here.
Next.
And so as soon as it's again, it's
creating content. We have our intro
section,
form section, footer section,
services, appointments.
There you go.
Pages. We have about, contact.
We can throw a course page in there if
we want.
Colors are a little bland. Let's pull in
one of these better colors.
I kind of like
this one right here. Okay,
we go. We can change the fonts.
So, it's really cool is how it lets you
kind of go in here and tweak this. And
now you have a whole site built using AI
that you can put your content into.
Create your lad magnets right here.
Built right into Squarespace. We go
under pages.
We could create a brand new page right
here.
Navigation.
Let's check out a page layout right
here.
Um, probably something for
see a general page.
This one's pretty good.
We're going to use this page. We can
then edit this, tweak this, adjust it.
You can add sections. Look, they have
templated sections right here. So, you
could go in, you could add, you know,
diff a different header. You can add in
um
contact, about, product,
service, portfolio, things like that.
And you can kind of model and create the
different kinds of sections
or just a blank section or you can throw
some text in.
This would be a blank section here.
We could
change the color of the section.
And so that's the beauty of using
Squarespace is you could literally
create sections, put a landing page
together very quickly that way. Now,
once we have that all put together, we
have our sales copy put together over in
chat GPT,
we could then go in and generate our
marketing materials. We could generate
our marketing content. We could generate
our
lead magnet copy. We could say generate
me
five versions of PAS copy.
I'll show you this on screen here. So
PAS copy is problem agitate solution.
I'll generate five versions and I'll say
convert those five versions into
written Facebook ads copy.
And you can see we're 12 minutes in and
we've already created the marketing
materials to generate a lead magnet that
you could use to go out there to
generate leads, get clients, and make
the kind of money that you want in your
business. Right now, it's thinking about
this. That's one of the things that GPT5
does is that it will think. There is
also GPT5 thinking model right here,
which is great.
Let's actually stop this, send it again
with GBT5 thinking model
and see what this generates. GBT5
thinking is going to be really good for
coming up with more complex
uh tasks. You got the GBT5 model. You
got GBT5 thinking. Okay,
here's the text right here for an ad.
Daily shoe fights, homework, standoffs.
When every request turns into a battle,
it's draining. Get 10 word for word
scripts that calm tense moments fast.
Feel like you're tiptoeing to avoid
meltdowns.
Living the playground shouldn't be a
public showdown. Like this is great.
This is awesome for that topic that
we're doing. Now, let's say that you're
not creating a something that's
necessarily for this niche. You can
steer it. You can direct chat GPT. We're
going to go back to GPT5. To do this,
we're going to say I want this to be
focused more on teenagers.
Okay, I'll adapt these more towards
teenagers. Every conversation is a
debate. Every request feels like walking
into a storm. If you're raising a teen
with autism, ADHD, or sensory
activities, you know how quickly they
can spiral. Okay, so this could be ads
that you can create. Generate me 10
versions of social media content ideas
for this niche to promote my lead
magnet. And this is again what chat GPT
can do. It can literally go through
and generate you ideas for different
pieces of content. POV style, acting as
a parent, knocking on bedroom, showing
script subtitles.
This is just one script. Get the full
set for free. Let's take this right
here.
Map out this entire social media
content.
So, we're going to tell it, okay, like
this doesn't give us much ideas, but we
can tell it to expand upon it and give
us more ideas as far as this goes. When
your teen is in a mood,
hey, you seem upset. I want to talk. I
want to talk now or later.
Opening the door later is fine. Okay,
I'm here when you're ready. You could
literally just show like you talking and
the script is on screen with some music.
And this would actually be a great
social media content right here. Great
piece of content for an Instagram reel.
So again, you can see
using AI allows you to generate content,
come up with ways to generate leads, and
if you're a coach, if you're a mentor,
if you're a service provider, it's one
of the best ways to find people that
need what you offer. Now, ultimately,
you're going to have to learn how to
take those people and sell to them. Just
generating leads of people without
selling to people is not going to be
effective. And so, what you need to do
is you need to learn how to get people
to go from interested to purchasing with
you. And that's what we do inside of my
Wealthy Coach Academy program is we show
you how to take people from interested
to purchasing with you. We help you dial
in all of the aspects of generating
leads, getting clients, using AI to
produce the results that you want. Each
week, we walk you through step by step
different aspect of your business live,
as well as we have a number of
pre-recorded classes and courses that
you can take. Go jump in, check out one
of the links in the description below.
We'll see you in there. Talk soon.
[Music]
[Applause]